const quiz3data = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "___ you ___ the shopping by 6 o'clock?",
    answersList: [
      {answer: "Will / have done", isCorrect: true},
      {answer: "Will / have been doing", isCorrect: false},
    ],
    help: "We use the future perfect to say that something will be ended, completed, or achieved by a particular point in the future."
 },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "By summer, Daniel ___ as project manager for five years.",
    answersList: [
      {answer: "will have worked", isCorrect: false},
      {answer: "will have been working", isCorrect: true},
    ],
    help: "We use the future perfect continuous to talk about an event that will be in progress for some time before a specified time in the future."
 },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "The train ___ by now.",
    answersList: [
      {answer: "will have left", isCorrect: true},
      {answer: "will be living", isCorrect: false},
    ],
    help: "We use the future perfect to make assumptions about something that has probably happened."
 },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "On Saturday, we ___ in this house for a year.",
    answersList: [
      {answer: "will have been living", isCorrect: true},
      {answer: "will have lived", isCorrect: false},
    ],
    help: "We use the future perfect continuous to emphasize how long something has been going on by a particular point in the future."
 },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Next month I _____ John for 10 years.",
    answersList: [
      {answer: "will have been knowing", isCorrect: false},
      {answer: "will have known", isCorrect: true},
    ],
    help: "We don't usually use the future perfect continuous with stative verbs."
 },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "By the time we get on the plane, they ___ the luggage.",
    answersList: [
      {answer: "will have already loaded", isCorrect: true},
      {answer: "will load", isCorrect: false},
    ],
    help: "We use the future perfect to talk about an event that will be finished and complete before a specified time in the future."
 },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "By the year 2050, scientists ___ a cure for cancer.",
    answersList: [
      {answer: "will discover", isCorrect: false},
      {answer: "will have discovered", isCorrect: true},
    ],
    help: "We use the future perfect to talk about an action that will finish before a certain time in the future, but we don't know exactly when."
 },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "By the next month, I ____ this book for 3 years.",
    answersList: [
      {answer: "will have been writing", isCorrect: true},
      {answer: "will have written", isCorrect: false},
    ],
    help: "We use the future perfect continuous to emphasize how long something has been going on by a particular point in the future. "
 },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Do you think that Dad ____ my bike for tomorrow?",
    answersList: [
      {answer: "will fix", isCorrect: false},
      {answer: "will have fixed", isCorrect: true},
    ],
    help: "We use the future perfect to make predictions about future events that will be completed before a specified future time."
 },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Next year they ___ married for 24 years.",
    answersList: [
      {answer: "will have been", isCorrect: true},
      {answer: "will be", isCorrect: false},
    ],
    help: "We use the future perfect to say that something will be achieved by a particular point in the future."
 },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "By the end of this week, we ____ for six months.",
    answersList: [
      {answer: "will be dating", isCorrect: false},
      {answer: "will have been dating", isCorrect: true},
    ],
    help: "We use the future perfect continuous to emphasize how long something has been going on by a particular point in the future."
 },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "Please, come at 8. By that time, I ___ my homework and we can go out.",
    answersList: [
      {answer: "will have finished", isCorrect: true},
      {answer: "will be finishing", isCorrect: false},
    ],
    help: "We use the future perfect to talk about an action that will be completed before a future time. "
 },
]
export default quiz3data
